Let's go over some external
components,
jams and supplies.
So I'm going to open up each
compartment where jams
might occur.
Anything green or blue inside the
machine is safe
to touch or maneuver, and they're
all labeled.
So the FS2 means finisher,
component two,
and anything blue means supplies or
sensors.
So this is your hole punch you'll
empty out when it's
full.
If you have that component, when
this is empty,
this will move forward, and you're
replacing this
clear cartridge here in this blue
piece here.
And there's a picture illustration
here to help guide
you through that.
You have an external stapler here
with this finisher
up to 50 sheets.
Print or copy.
So anything you want stapled,
just insert.
Again, up to 50 sheets.
Not very much green in here.
There's three green, M2, M1, and M3,
but generally in here you see the
paper sticking out.
It's really hot in here, so be
careful,
but I recommend pulling it out with
two hands so nothing
rips off and causes further issues
where you might
need a tech. And with this door,
you kind of have to use some force
when closing it.
And here, sometimes people forget to
remove their
staples or their paper clips, and
this is a part you
might have to open here.
This is DF1.
But again, just a reminder,
you'll see
some guided instructions, very
detailed.
So it shows that I've opened that
component,
but you'll also see some text
guiding you.
Again, it might say open DF1, turn
FS5,
turn FS1.
And this little hand here indicates
you have to close
it correctly by pushing there.
And your ADF, this is a sensor also,
holds up to 300 sheets.
And just more on the sensors.
If I load this and this sensor gets
maneuvered,
moved,
it's beeping at me.
Why are you beeping at me?
I can look at that message center.
It says paper is not, there's no
matching paper size
of A4.
But as soon as I adjust the sensor
back to eight and
a half by eleven, that message goes
away.
And there's your toner.
This pops out.
Out of box, pull off any orange tape
and insert the
toner.
Your waste toner box.
There's that blue.
This whole unit gets replaced.
When this is full, the machine is
non-operable.
So when you see this orange light
blinking,
look on that message center.
Right now it says it's warming up,
but you'll see this blinking.
It will say replace waste toner box
soon.
So these sensors are very important.
Always make sure they're adjusted to
the paper size in the
tray.
Let's say it gets maneuvered just a
little bit.
Someone's loading more paper or just
accidentally
gets maneuvered.
You never want to see question
marks.
So right now it's showing tray 1
question marks because
it's not detecting that size.
But as soon as I adjust,
the question marks go away and it
knows what tray
to pull from. So now when I'm
sending print or copy
jobs, it knows tray 1 has 8.5 x 11
and I'm going to
pull from that tray.
If you see these light up orange,
it means that tray is out of paper.
You have your flash drive option
here on the right
side. You can print and save to User
Box with your USB
drive.
Anything you scan on the glass,
make sure it's top left corner.
You see here there's a ruler so it
goes by paper size
and top left corner is 8.5 x 11
start.
To order supplies or place a service
call,
call this 800 number and have this
eight-digit ID handy.
Or if you have the newer KM sticker,
you have a QR code here which you
can use with your
phone to bring up the app to place a
service call
for service or supplies.
So thank you. I hope that helped.
I'm creating videos in increments,
so that was external.
I'll do one on copying and I'll do
one on scanning.
And I hope it helps you until I can
get on site.